In one take. No mistake. For God's sake!
Failure! is a comedy, drama, thriller film directed by Alex Kahuam.
Shot in a single, 87-minute take, James has just one hour to choose
between financial ruin or murder to protect his family.
James, played by Ted Raimi.
Mr. Serge, played by Merrick McCartha.
Maria, played by Melissa Diaz.
Unknown Man, played by Noel Douglas Orput.
Jessica, played by Christin Muuli.
Alvar, played by Daniel Kuhlman.
is a 2023 crime comedy film written and directed by Alex Kahuam.
The film stars Ted Raimi, Merrick McCartha, Noel Douglas
Orput, Melissa Diaz and Christin Muuli.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and intense.